(Sheldon:)Yes, hello.
Uh, this is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)I'm at 2311
North Los Robles Avenue.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to report
a dangerous wild animal.
(Sheldon:)A blue jay.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, this is Animal Control.
I don't understand the laughter.
(Sheldon:)No, the bird is not in my home.
(Sheldon:)If he was in my home,
I obviously would've called 911.
(Sheldon:)I have no doubt that there are things
that you're frightened of.
Uh, being stuck in a dead-end
public service job.
(Sheldon:)Or your wife stepping out on you...
(Sheldon:)...because you're stuck
in a dead-end public service job.
(Sheldon:)Or spiders.
(Sheldon:)Don't you think
I tried making cat noises?
(Leonard(returning in a tee shirt and backwards cap):)Too casual?
(Sheldon:)For an audience with the Queen, yes.